Guide to the Washington State University Photographs, Subject File 1892-1999
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Washington State University Photographs, Subject File
1892-1999
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
PC 4
32.75 Linear feet of shelf space 66 Boxes
This collection of assorted images depicting the history of the State College of Washington (later Washington State University) covers a wide range of subjects, including photographs of buildings on campus, students, faculty, University regents, and campus visitors.
This collection of assorted images depicting the history of the State College of Washington (later Washington State University) covers a wide range of subjects, including photographs of buildings on campus, students, faculty, University regents, and campus visitors.
The positive and negative images in this collection were arranged into two separate series; however, it should be made clear that images in the two series do not necessarily overlap - the majority of the negatives and not present as positives, and vice versa. The sub-division of the subjects can be quite extensive. For example, Athletics is arranged alphabetically by individual sports and each sport is subdivided chronologically. If one were looking for a photograph of the 1945 Basketball team, one would first look under Athletics, then Basketball, then 1945. One should check the positives first, then the negatives. During initial processing, a series of "sports contact sheet prints," covering primarily the 1940s and 1950s, was retained as a separate subseries (1.1.05) within sports positives. So, someone looking for sports images in this era should check this subseries as well. Regents and Faculty members have been arranged into subdivisions alphabetically by name.
The collection continues to grow as loose single images are added and interfiled over time.
The collection is divided into positive and negative images, each arranged in alphabetical order by subject. Several of the subject areas have been sub-divided into minor headings which are arranged either chronologically or alphabetically. The arrangement of the subseries within each of the two series (positive images, and negative images) is identical - subseries 1.8 in the positives will be the same subject as subseries 2.8 in the negatives.
This collection is open and available for research use.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Washington State University -- Students -- Photographs; State College of Washington -- Students -- Photographs; Washington State University -- Faculty -- Photographs; State College of Washington -- Faculty -- Photographs; Washington State University -- History -- Photographs; State College of Washington -- History -- Photographs; Washington State University; State College of Washington
College students -- Photographs; Universities and colleges -- Washington (State) -- History -- Photographs
Colleges and Universities; Washington (State); Photographs
- Series 1: Positive Images
  - Subseries 1.1: Athletics
    - Subseries 1.1.01: Baseball
      - 1901-1919 (Box 1)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 1)
      - 1900-1939 (Box 1)
      - 1930-1939 (Box 1)
      - 1940-1959 (Box 1)
      - 1930-1959 (Box 1)
      - 1960-1970 (Box 1)
      - 1960-1971 (Box 1)
    - Subseries 1.1.02: Basketball
      - Subseries 1.1.02.1: Team Pictures
        - 1901, 1904-1905, 1907 (Box 1)
        - 1921-1944, 1947-1949 (Box 1)
      - Subseries 1.1.02.2: Players and Action Shots
        - Games, 1941 (Box 1)
        - Players, 1930-1949 (Box 1)
        - Players, 1950s-19702 (Box 2)
        - Games, 1958-1959 (Box 2)
        - Games, 1960 (Box 2)
        - Games, 1961 (Box 2)
        - Games, 1962-1963 (Box 2)
        - Players, 1965-1969 (Box 2)
        - Games, undated (Box 2)
      - Frosh Basketball (Box 2)
      - Intramurals, Managers, other schools (Box 2)
      - Slides 1970s-1980s (Box 2)
      - Slides 1985 (Box 2a)
    - Boxing (Box 2a)
    - Subseries 1.1.03: Coaches
      - Buck Bailey (Box 2a)
      - Orin "Babe" Hollingbery (also see Faculty) (Box 2a)
      - Individual Pictures of Coaches (Box 2a)
      - In Groups: 1915-1950 (Box 2a)
      - In Groups: 1951- (Box 2a)
    - Fencing (Box 3)
    - Subseries 1.1.04: Football
      - Coaches (Box 3)
      - 1894-1904 (Box 3)
      - 1905-1908 (Box 3)
      - 1909-1913 (Box 3)
      - 1913 (Box 3)
      - 1914-1915 (Box 3)
      - 1950 (Box 3)
      - Rose Bowl Team, 1916 (Box 4)
      - Rose Bowl, 1916 (Box 4)
      - 1916 (Box 4)
      - 1917-1919 (Box 4)
      - 1920-1939 (Box 4)
      - 1920-1923 (Box 4)
      - 1924-1926 (Box 4)
      - 1927-1929 (Box 4)
      - 1930-1933 (Box 4)
      - Rose Bowl, 1931 (Box 4)
      - 1934-1939 (Box 5)
      - 1940-1942 (Box 5)
      - 1940-1959 (Box 5)
      - ca. 1946 (Box 5)
      - 1946-1949 (Box 5)
      - 1951-1955 (Box 5)
      - 1956-1958 (Box 6)
      - 1958 (Box 6)
      - 1959 (Box 6)
      - 1960-1979 (Box 6)
      - 1960 (Box 6)
      - 1961-1965 (Box 6)
      - 1966-1967 (Box 6)
      - 1968 (Box 6)
      - 1969 (Box 6)
      - 1970-1972 (Box 6)
      - Slides 1984-1985 (Box 6)
      - Heroes ca. 1989 (Box 6)
      - 1980s (Box 6)
      - 1997 Rose Bowl photo (Box 6)
      - Halftimes (Box 6)
    - Subseries 1.1.05: All Sports, Contact Prints, 1947-1956 (bulk)
      - Baseball, 1936 (Box 7)
      - Baseball, 1953 (Box 7)
      - Baseball, 1954 (Box 7)
      - Baseball, 1955 (Box 7)
      - Baseball, 1956 (Box 7)
      - Basketball, undated (Box 7)
      - Basketball, 1935-1936 (Box 7)
      - Basketball, 1950-1951 (Box 7)
      - Basketball, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
      - Basketball, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
      - Basketball, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
      - Basketball, 1954-1955 (Box 7)
      - Basketball, 1955-1956 (Box 7)
      - Basketball, 1956-1957 (Box 7)
      - Boxing, 1951-1952 (Box 7)
      - Boxing, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
      - Boxing, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
      - Boxing, 1954-1955 (Box 7)
      - Boxing, 1956 (Box 7)
      - Fencing, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
      - Fishing, 1953-1954 (Box 7)
      - Football, undated (Box 7)
      - Football, 1947 (Box 8)
      - Football, 1948 (Box 8)
      - Football, 1950 (Box 8)
      - Football, 1951 (Box 8)
      - Football, 1952 (Box 8)
      - Football, 1953 (Box 8)
      - Football, 1954 (Box 8)
      - Football, 1955 (Box 8)
      - Football, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Golf, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Gymnastics, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
      - Gymnastics, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Gymnastics, 1954-1955 (Box 9)
      - Gymnastics, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Gymnastics, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
      - Intramurals, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
      - Intramurals, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Skiing, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
      - Skiing, 1953-1954 (Box 9)
      - Skiing, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Swimming, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
      - Swimming, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Swimming, 1954 (Box 9)
      - Swimming, 1954-1955 (Box 9)
      - Swimming, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Tennis, 1952 (Box 9)
      - Tennis, 1954 (Box 9)
      - Track, 1952; includes Interscholastic Meet (Box 9)
      - Track, 1953 (Box 9)
      - Track, 1954 (Box 9)
      - Track, 1955 (Box 9)
      - Track, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Women's sports, ca. 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Wrestling, 1951-1952 (Box 9)
      - Wrestling, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Wrestling, 1953-1954 (Box 9)
      - Wrestling, 1954-1955 (Box 9)
      - Wrestling, 1956 (Box 9)
      - Miscellaneous, inc. baseball, basketball, football, skiing, 1949-1950 (Box 9)
      - Miscellaneous, mostly sports awards, 1952-1953 (Box 9)
      - Miscellaneous, sports trophies & swimming, 1956 (Box 9)
    - Golf (Box 10)
    - Subseries 1.1.06: Gymnastics
      - 1900-1949 (Box 10)
      - 1950-1979 (Box 10)
    - High School Track (Box 10)
    - High School Wrestling (Box 10)
    - Mascots (Box 10)
    - Skiers (Box 10)
    - Ski Team (Box 10)
    - Soccer (Box 10)
    - Subseries 1.1.07: Swimming
      - 1925-1949 (Box 10)
      - 1950-1979 (Box 10)
    - Subseries 1.1.08: Tennis
      - 1920-1949 (Box 10)
      - 1950 (Box 10)
    - Subseries 1.1.09: Track
      - Action Shots, 1906 (Box 11)
      - Team Pictures and Individuals, 1901-1908 (Box 11)
      - Team Pictures and Individuals, 1909 (Box 11)
      - Track Meets, 1909 (Box 11)
      - 1909-1920 (Box 11)
      - 1910-1920 (Box 11)
      - Track Meets, 1910-1915 (Box 11)
      - Track Meets, 1916-1919 (Box 11)
      - Team Pictures and Individuals, 1910-1916 (Box 11)
      - Team Pictures and Individuals, 1917-1926 (Box 11)
      - Track Meets, 1920-1925 (Box 11)
      - Team Pictures and Individuals, 1927-1929 (Box 12)
      - Track Meets, 1926-1929 (Box 12)
      - Team Pictures and Individuals, 1930-1939 (Box 12)
      - Individual Action Shots, 1935-1939 (Box 12)
      - Team Pictures and Individuals, 1940-1949 (Box 12)
      - Team Pictures and Individuals, 1950-1959 (Box 12)
      - Track Meets, 1960 (Box 12)
      - Track Meets, 1961 (Box 12)
      - Team Pictures and Individuals, 1960-1969 (Box 12)
      - Actions Shots, 1960-1969 (Box 12)
      - Cross Country (Box 12)
      - Managers (Box 12)
      - Interscholastic, 1907-1960 (Box 12)
      - Interscholastic, 1960 (Box 12)
      - Track 1970s (Box 12)
      - Slides 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - Subseries 1.1.10: Women's Athletics
      - 1900-1939 (Box 13)
      - 1940 (Box 13)
      - Women's Basketball slides 1985 (Box 13)
    - Subseries 1.1.11: Wrestling
      - 1909-1949 (Box 13)
      - 1950- (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Athletics and Activities (Box 13)
  - Subseries 1.2: Campus
    - Subseries 1.2.1: Aerial Views
      - 1893-1899 (Box 14)
      - 1900-1905 (Box 14)
      - 1906-1910 (Box 14)
      - 1909 (Box 14)
      - 1910 (Box 14)
      - 1911-1919 (Box 14)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 14)
      - 1930-1939 (Box 15)
      - 1932-1939 (Box 15)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 15)
      - 1949 (Box 15)
      - 1950-1959 (Box 15)
      - 1960-1969 (Box 15)
      - 1970 (Box 15)
    - Athletic Fields (Box 15)
    - PQ Cougar Camp (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous Campus Buildings (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Pullman Photos (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Campus Scenes (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous WSC and Pullman Scenes by Earl Philippi, 1924-1926 (Box 16)
    - Building Groups (Box 16b)
    - Building Groups, campus paving, 1934 (Box 16b)
    - Greek Houses (Box 16b)
    - Library (Box 16b)
    - Silver Lake (Box 16b)
    - Train Station Scenes (Box 16b)
    - Winter Fun Scenes (Box 16b)
    - Winter Scenes (Box 16b)
  - Subseries 1.3: Classes
    - Architecture (Box 17)
    - Child Development (Box 17)
    - Education (Box 17)
    - Extension Division (Box 17)
    - Fine Arts (Box 17)
    - Foreign Language Lab. (Box 17)
    - KWSU Radio (Box 17)
    - Nursery School 1975 (Box 17)
    - P.E. - Men (Box 17)
    - P.E. - Women (Box 17)
    - Short Courses (Box 17)
    - Summer School (Box 17)
    - Students in Miscellaneous Classes/Classrooms (Box 17)
  - Subseries 1.4: Commencement
    - 1892-1947 (Box 18)
    - 1947 (Box 18)
    - 1953 (Box 18)
    - 1954 (Box 18)
    - 1955 (Box 18)
    - 1956 (Box 18)
    - 1957 (Box 18)
    - 1958 (Box 18)
    - 1959 (Box 18)
    - 1960 (Box 19)
    - 1961 (Box 19)
    - 1962 (Box 19)
    - 1963 (Box 19)
    - 1964 (Box 19)
    - 1965 (Box 19)
    - 1966 (Box 19)
    - 1967 (Box 19)
    - 1968 (Box 19)
    - 1969 (Box 19)
    - 1970, 1973, 1974 (Box 19)
    - 1975 (Box 19)
    - 1977- (Box 19)
    - 1983- (Box 19)
    - Unsorted duplicates (Box 19)
    - 2000- (Box 19)
  - Subseries 1.5: Conferences
    - Agricultural (Box 20)
    - Bankers Conference (Box 20)
    - Dairy/Agronomy (Box 20)
    - Education (Box 20)
    - High School Summer Camp (Box 20)
    - National Science Foundation Workshop, 1975 (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20)
  - Subseries 1.6: Equipment
    - Instruments (Box 20)
    - Machinery (Box 20)
    - Nuclear Reactor (Box 20)
    - WSC Power Plant (Box 20)
  - Subseries 1.7: Events
    - Activity Round Up (Box 20)
    - Awards and Banquets (Box 20)
    - Alumni Banquet (Box 20)
    - Award Presentations (Box 20)
    - Campus Day (Box 20)
    - Campus Day, 1912-1916 (Box 21)
    - Campus Day. Photos by Lawrence Shea, May 19, 1922 (Box 21)
    - Dad's Day, 1958-1959 (Box 21)
    - Dad's Day, 1960-1962 (Box 21)
    - Dad's Day, ca. 1930s (Box 21)
    - Dances (Miscellaneous) (Box 21)
    - Elections - Signs, Watch night, Voting (Box 21)
    - Farm Demonstration Train (Box 21)
    - Foundation Day, 1911 (Box 21)
    - Freshman-Faculty Weekend (Box 21)
    - Frosh.-Soph. Supremacy (Box 21)
    - Harvest Ball and Harvest Queen (Box 22)
    - Homecoming - Queen, Dance, Rally (Box 22)
    - Horticulture Exhibitions (Box 22)
    - Junior Prom (Box 22)
    - Little International (Box 22)
    - Livestock Shows (Box 22)
    - May Fete / May Pole Dance (Box 22)
    - May Queen (Box 22)
    - Military Ball (Box 22)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 22)
    - Library (Box 23)
    - Mock Wedding, Stevens Hall, 1905 (Box 23)
    - Mother's Weekend (Box 23)
    - Murrow Symposium (Box 23)
    - Parties and Picnics (Box 23)
    - Racism Workshops, 1969-1970 (Box 23)
    - Rallies (Box 23)
    - Registration (Box 23)
    - Sophomore Tolo (Box 23)
    - Student Strikes and Protests, 1936 (Box 23)
    - Student Strikes and Protests, 1970 (Box 23)
    - Woman's Day (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 23)
  - Subseries 1.8: Exhibits
    - Campus - Ag. Eng., Ag. Sci., Hort., Dairy, Art, Misc. (Box 23)
    - Library (Box 23)
  - Subseries 1.9: Experimental Stations
    - Agricultural (Box 24)
    - Central Washington (Box 24)
    - Dry Farming - Waterville (Box 24)
    - Dry Land - Adams Branch (Box 24)
    - Exhibits and Fairs (Box 24)
    - Irrigation - Prosser (Box 24)
    - Livestock (Box 24)
    - Long Beach Station (Box 24)
    - Marine Station (Box 24)
    - Palouse Conservation Field Station (Box 25)
    - Pullman Station (Box 25)
    - Puyallup Station (Box 25)
    - Puyallup Summer Sessions (Box 25)
    - Tree Fruit - Wenatchee (Box 25)
    - Walla Walla State Prison Crops (Box 25)
    - Western and Southwestern Washington (Box 25)
  - Subseries 1.10: Faculty
    - A (Box 26)
    - Armstrong, Cliff (Box 26)
    - B (Box 26)
    - Bohler, J. Fred (Box 26)
    - C (Box 26)
    - D (Box 26)
    - Drucker, A.E. (Box 26)
    - E (Box 26)
    - F (Box 26)
    - Foote, William Wirt (Box 26)
    - French, Dr. and Mrs. C. Clement (Box 26)
    - G (Box 26)
    - H (Box 26)
    - I-J (Box 27a)
    - Johnson, E.C. (Box 27a)
    - K (Box 27a)
    - Kimbrough, Herbert (Box 27a)
    - Faculty (Box 27a)
    - L (Box 27a)
    - M (Box 27a)
    - McCoy, John E. (Box 27a)
    - N (Box 27a)
    - O - P (Box 27a)
    - R (Box 27a)
    - S (Box 27a)
    - T (Box 27a)
    - U - V (Box 27a)
    - W (Box 27a)
    - Waller, Omar Lysander (Box 27a)
    - X - Y - Z (Box 27a)
    - Group Pictures (list included) (Box 27b)
    - Group Pictures (Box 27b)
    - Faculty - Engineering Group Photos (Box 27b)
  - Subseries 1.11: Graduating Classes
    - 1897-1899 (Box 28)
    - 1900-1909 (Box 28)
    - 1910-1920 (Box 28)
    - 1921 (Box 28)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 28)
  - Subseries 1.12: Greek Letter Organizations
    - Events (Box 28)
    - Fraternities (Box 28)
    - Sororities (Box 28)
  - Subseries 1.13: Laboratories
    - Agriculture (Box 29)
    - Albrook Hydraulic Laboratory (Box 29)
    - Anthropology - Aswan Relocation (Box 29)
    - Audiovisual in Library 1964 (Box 29)
    - Audiovisual Labs (Box 29)
    - Audiovisual Center (Box 29)
    - Broadcast and Recording (Box 29)
    - Dairy Science (Box 29)
    - Easter Seals Research (Box 29)
    - Engineering (Box 29)
    - Geology (Box 29)
    - Home Economics (Box 29)
    - Laboratory Work (Box 30)
    - Machine Shop (Box 30)
    - Meats and Poultry (Box 30)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 30)
    - Peace Corps (Box 30)
    - Research (Box 30)
    - Sciences (Box 31)
    - Textiles (Box 31)
    - Veterinary (Box 31-32)
    - Wheat Laboratory (Box 32)
    - Woodworking (Box 32)
    - WSC 1956 (Box 32)
  - Subseries 1.14: Livestock
    - Cattle (Box 32)
    - Horses (Box 32)
    - Swine (Pigs & Hogs) (Box 32)
    - Poultry (Box 32)
    - Sheep (Box 32)
  - Subseries 1.15: Organizations
    - Alpha Phi Sigma (Box 33)
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers (Box 33)
    - Associated Students of the College of Agriculture (Box 33)
    - British Empire Club (Box 33)
    - Cheerleaders (Box 33)
    - Cosmopolitan Club (Box 33)
    - Debate (Box 33)
    - Erani Club (Box 33)
    - Evergreen 1 (Box 33)
    - Evergreen 2 (Box 33)
    - Food Service (Box 33)
    - 4-H (Box 33)
    - 4-H - Junior Extension Work (Box 33)
    - Future Farmers of America (FFA) (Box 33)
    - Grey W (Box 33)
    - Hawaiian Club (Box 33)
    - Honors Program (Box 33)
    - Intercollegiate Knights and Victory Bell (Box 33)
    - Organizations (Box 34)
    - Livestock Judging Team (Box 34)
    - KWSU -TV (Box 34)
    - Mortar Board (Box 34)
    - Radio and Television Services (Box 34)
    - Spurs (Box 34)
    - Washington Literary Society (Box 34)
    - Washington State Women's Club (Box 34)
    - Wrangler's Club (Box 34)
    - WSU Agriculturalist Staff (Box 34)
    - Websterian Society (Box 34)
    - YMCA (Box 34)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 34)
  - Subseries 1.16: Performing Arts
    - Subseries 1.16.1: Drama
      - 1901-1949 (Box 34)
      - 1950 (Box 34)
    - Bank (Box 34)
    - Mug Band (Box 34)
    - Mug-Glee Club (Box 34)
    - Music (Box 35)
    - Orchestra (Box 35)
    - Theater (Box 35)
  - Subseries 1.17: Presidents
    - Lilley, George - May 1891 - December 1892 (Box 35)
    - Heston, John W. - December 1892 - August 1893 (Box 35)
    - Bryan, Enoch A. - August 1893 - December 1915 (Box 35)
    - Holland, Ernest O. (portraits) - January 1916 - December 1944 (Box 35a)
    - Holland, Ernest O. (with others) (Box 35a)
    - Compton, Wilson M. - January 1945 - March 1962 (Box 35a)
    - French, C. Clement - April 1952 - 1966 (Box 35a)
    - Terrell, W. Glenn (Box 35b)
    - Terrell, W. Glenn (with family) (Box 35b)
    - Smith, Sam H. - 1985 - 2000 (Box 35c)
    - Rawlins, V. Lane - 2000 - 2007 (Box 36)
    - Floyd, Elson (Box 36)
  - Subseries 1.18: Regents
    - Allen, John Beard (Box 36)
    - Anderson, J. S. (Box 36)
    - Arrasmith, J. W. (Box 36)
    - Barnard, F. J. (Box 36)
    - Bellinger, J. H. (Box 36)
    - Blandford, Henry S. (Box 36)
    - Browne, J. J. (Box 36)
    - Canfield, H. W. (Box 36)
    - Coman, E. T. (Box 36)
    - Connor, Charles R. (Box 36)
    - Conover, D. B. (Box 36)
    - Crow, H. D. (Box 36)
    - Cunningham, James C. (Box 36)
    - Davis, Arthur (Box 36)
    - Dunn, A. D. (Box 36)
    - Edmiston, J. E. (Box 36)
    - Ettinger, U. L. (Box 36)
    - Fellows, Eugene J. (Box 36)
    - Gannon, George H. (Box 36)
    - Gose, T. P. (Box 36)
    - Hopp, George W. (Box 36)
    - Hulbert, J. H. (Box 36)
    - Ingraham, Edward (Box 36)
    - Johnson, Lee A. (Box 36)
    - Kimbrough, S. A. (Box 36)
    - Lesh, Daniel E. (Box 36)
    - Mays, F. W. D. (Box 36)
    - McAllister, Charles E. (Box 36)
    - McCroskey, R. C. (Box 36)
    - McGregor, Peter (Box 36)
    - Neff, Lyle (Box 36)
    - Orton, Charles W. (Box 36)
    - Pease, W. M. (Box 36)
    - Perham, B. A. (Box 36)
    - Ritz, W. A. (Box 37)
    - Rowe, W. R. (Box 37)
    - Sharp, John P. (Box 37)
    - Smith, Andrew H. (Box 37)
    - Stearns, J. W. (Box 37)
    - Stimson, Fred J. (Box 37)
    - Tannatt, T.R. (Box 37)
    - Troy, D. S. (Box 37)
    - Wilmer, F. J. (Box 37)
    - Windus, Walter V. (Box 37)
    - Witt, George (Box 37)
    - Group Pictures (Box 37)
  - Subseries 1.19: ROTC
    - 1894-1899 (Box 37)
    - 1900-1909 (Box 37)
    - 1900-1909 (Box 37)
    - 1910-1919 (Box 38)
    - 1920-1929 (Box 38)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 38)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 38)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 38)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 38)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 38)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 39)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 39)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 39)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 39-40)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 40)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 40)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 40)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 40)
    - 1946-1947 (Box 40)
    - 1949 (Box 40)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 41)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 41)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 41)
    - 1955-1957 (Box 41)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 41)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 41)
    - 1961-1962 (Box 41)
    - 1963 (Box 41)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 41)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 41)
    - 1966-1967 (Box 41)
    - 1967-1968 (Box 42)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 42)
    - 1970-1971 (Box 42)
    - 1972 (Box 42)
    - 1973 (Box 42-43)
    - 1974 (Box 43)
    - 1975 (Box 43)
    - 1976 (Box 43)
    - Air Force (Box 43)
    - Women's Sponsor Club Pt, 1929 (Box 44)
  - Subseries 1.19.1: Women Sponsors
    - 1930-1939 (Box 44)
    - 1950-1959 (Box 44)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 44)
    - 1970 (Box 44)
    - Unidentified and Undated (Box 44)
  - Subseries 1.20: Staff Personnel
    - Former Animal Science Staff B-L (Box 45)
    - Former Animal Science Staff M-W (Box 45)
    - Glassblower - George Harnes (Box 45)
    - Northwest Assessment of Collegiate Registrars (Box 45)
    - Placement Bureau (Box 45)
    - Retirement of Guy Brislawn, 1966 (Box 45)
    - Unidentified (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous - identified (Box 45)
  - Subseries 1.21: Students
    - Studying (Box 45)
    - Subseries 1.21.1: Men
      - Men - Identified and dated, mounted portraits, 1911-1913 (Box 45)
      - Men - Identified and dated, 1892-1920 (Box 46)
      - 1892-1939 (Box 46)
      - 1931 (Box 46)
      - Unidentified pre 1939 (Box 46)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 46)
      - 1950 (Box 46)
    - Subseries 1.21.2: Women
      - 1892-1939 Identified (Box 47)
      - 1892-1939 (Box 47)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 47)
      - 1950 (Box 47)
    - Subseries 1.21.3: Alumni
      - Alumni (Box 47)
      - Alumni and Golden Grads (Box 48)
    - Subseries 1.21.4: Students in Groups
      - 1892-1910 (Box 48)
      - 1911-1919 (Box 48)
      - 1920-1929 (Box 48)
      - 1930-1939 (Box 48)
      - 1940 (Box 48)
      - In Groups: Dorms (Box 49)
      - In Groups Unidentified females (Box 49)
      - In Groups Unidentified males (Box 49)
      - In Groups (Miscellaneous and undated) (Box 49)
      - In Groups (Unidentified) (Box 49)
      - 1977-1978 Identified (Box 49)
      - Married Students (Box 49)
      - International Students (Box 49)
      - Chinese Club (Box 49)
  - Subseries 1.22: Visitors to Campus
    - Authors (Box 50)
    - Dignitaries and Politicians (Box 50)
    - 4-H Club Camp, 1935 (Box 50)
    - Sichuan Province Education Delegation, 1981 (Box 50)
    - Lecturers (Box 50)
    - Musicians and Concerts (Box 50)
    - Sports (Box 50)
    - Theater (Box 50)
  - Subseries 1.23: Veterinary Scholarship Awards
    - 1979 (Box 50)
    - 1980 (Box 50)
    - 1981 (Box 50)
- Series 2: Negatives
  - Subseries 2.1: Athletics
    - Baseball, 1960-1970 (Box 51)
    - Baseball, 1960-1971 (Box 51)
    - Basketball Freshman Team, 1958-1961 (Box 51)
    - Basketball Games, 1958-1959 (Box 51)
    - Basketball Games, 1960 (Box 51)
    - Basketball Games, 1961 (Box 51)
    - Basketball Players Action Shots, 1960's (Box 51)
    - Basketball, 1962-1963 (Box 51)
    - Boxing (Box 51)
    - Coaches: Buck Bailey (Box 51)
    - Coaches: Individual Shots (Box 51)
    - Football: Not Dated, 1920-1939 (Box 51)
    - Football, 1951-1955 (Box 51)
    - Football, 1958 (Box 51)
    - Football, 1959 (Box 51)
    - Contact Prints: Miscellaneous Sports, 1952-1953 (Box 52)
    - Contact Prints: Baseball, 1954 (Box 52)
    - Contact Prints: Basketball, 1954-1955 (Box 52)
    - Contact Prints: Track, 1954 (Box 52)
    - Contact Prints: Boxing, Wrestling, Swimming, etc., 1956 (Box 52)
    - Football, 1960 (Box 52)
    - Football: Not Dated, 1960-1979 (Box 52)
    - Football, 1966-1967 (Box 52)